http://www.savingantiquities.org/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
We recognize that you may have an interest in how we collect, retain and use information about you via this web site. SAFE has created this Privacy Policy statement to demonstrate our commitment to the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. Currently we do not collect any information about our web site viewers through the use of “cookies,” which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. If, however, in the future, we decide to use this technology, the information we collect from “cookies” will be solely used for the purpose of better understanding our users and their use of the web site.
SAFE will not share or release information collected about you through this web site to third parties, unless we receive your prior written consent or we are required by law to release information to the recipient. SAFE may, however, produce internal reports that analyze user activity in anonymous aggregated form.
The SAFE web site is protected with a variety of security measures. We employ a variety of mechanisms to ensure that any data we provide is free of viruses, worms and other malicious code known as of the date the information was originally posted to the SAFE web site. We also employ mechanisms to ensure that any data you provide to us is not lost, misused, or altered inappropriately.
The information collected in our Volunteer Enrollment Form is also subject to the Google Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this web site or your dealings with us, please contact us. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a new policy at this location.
ABOUT US
STAFF
BOARD
WHY ANTIQUITIES
WHY PUBLIC AWARENESS
WHY SAFE
OUR STORY
OUR PRINCIPLES
US RESPONSE
WHY SHOULD YOU CARE?
FACTS & FIGURES
RESOURCES
BLOG
SAFECONNECT
COUNTRY OVERVIEWS
EVENTS, CAMPAIGNS, TOOLS
SAFE BEACON AWARDS
SAFE TOURS
SAFE/Saving Antiquities for Everyone
© . All Rights Reserved. SAFE is a nonprofit 501(c)(3) organization, and contributions are tax deductible under section 170 of the Internal Revenue Code.
Please read our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.
Our address: SAFE/Saving Antiquities for Everyone Inc.
66-10 149th Street, #4C
Flushing, New York 11367
USA
Type and Press “enter” to Search
